

# IBNU WILDAN

INFORMATICS ENGINEERING FRONT END DEVELOPER

#### PERSONAL DATA

TANGERANG, 24 JULI 1995

GENDRE : MALE RELIGION: ISLAM

## CONTACT



https://wildaninu.com



085217180396



ibnuwildann@gmail.com

## HOBBY



Tracking



Football



Enduro motorbikes

#### ABOUT

I'm a front-end developer focused on creating visually stunning and intuitive web experiences. With expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React Js, using front-end frameworks with React. as well as back-end experience in expertise with Node Js, Express Js, Rest API, MYSQL and postman. I make sure that every website I build not only looks great, but also functions smoothly. As a UI designer, I pay attention to every detail in design to create user interfaces that are easy to use and enjoyable for users. I also ensure that every web layout I create follows responsive design and modern design principles to provide the best user experience. With a combination of technical skills and design artistry, I am ready to create engaging and intuitive web experiences for users.

#### ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

• Graduate of Informatic Enfineering, at Gunadarma University with GPA (3.23)

## COURSES & WORKSHOP

- Website & Mobile at Purwadhika digital school
- Courses "English" at LBPP LIA
- Courses "Oracle for Beginner" at Gunadarma University
- Workshop "Java" at Gunadarma University

## PROJECT & WORK EXPERIENCES

- Engineer & Administrator Learning Management System Yayasan Kristen Indonesia (Feb 2021-Currently employed) develop, design and managing hybrid learning management system
- Web & Mobile Project Purwadhika digital school (Oct 2020- Jan 2021) Develop Ecommerce web platform
- Administrator Customer Care Bank Negara Indonesia (Mart 2018 - Sep2020) Resolving banking problems related to online transactions made by customers
- Front End Developer PT. Total Bangun Persada (Oct 2017-Jan 2018) Design, develop and test UI for web platform

### SKILL&SUMMARY OF ATRIBUT

- Bussines Process Framework (React.JS, Node.Js, Express.JS)
- HTML, CSS, Javascrip, RESTful API, MYSQL, Routing, Bootstrap, GitHub, Postman, Blender, Unity.
- The Ability to Work Both Independently or as a Member of a Diversifed Team.
- Easily Adapt to Different Environments.
- · Able to Work With Different People and Different Management.
- Keen and Eager to Learn Something New.